zurmo.org 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy — Zurmo

**Information Gathered Through This Site**

This site tracks the domains from which people visit Zurmo, the number of visitors to each page of the site, browser type, IP addresses, and Zurmo may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information.

Users can generally visit the Site without revealing any personally identifiable information. However, in certain sections of the Site, Zurmo may, among other things, invite user to contact Zurmo, or complete a profile or registration form. Due to the nature of these activities, Zurmo may collect personally identifiable information such as: your name, contact data such as your address, email address, phone number, employment and company information; and other information that you voluntarily transmit with your communication to us. We may use the information collected to provide you with additional information about our services, promotions, and upcoming events. We provide you the option to “opt-out” of any promotional emails by clicking the ‘Unsubscribe’ link present at the end of every email we send out.

**With whom we share Information**

At no time, unless law requires such disclosure, disclosure is necessary to aid law enforcement, or a user specifically authorizes such disclosure, will Zurmo disclose individual user personal information that is not publicly available to unrelated third parties.

**Demo Login**

We understand that you may wish not to disclose your Personal Information for trying out our services, so we provide you the option of a Demo Login for our CRM products. The contents created by you using the Demo Login will be accessible to all persons using the Demo Login. Hence we specifically request you not to store your personal and sensitive information, files and documents while using the Demo Login as doing so would make them publicly available to all users.

**Forums**  
User names and email addresses (as well as any additional information that a user may choose to post) are publicly available on the Zurmo.org forum. Other users will be able to see any information that users post to such forums and Zurmo is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Cookies**

We use cookies on this Web site to enhance and customize your experience of our services. Temporary cookies will be removed from your computer each time you close your browser. A cookie is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server to be stored on your hard drive that allows easier access the next time the same page is visited. The use of cookies provides benefits to you, such as eliminating the need for you to enter your password frequently during a session. For these purposes, our cookies are tied to personally identifiable information. If you do not want your personal information to be stored by cookies, you can configure your browser so that it notifies you whenever a cookie is received so you can decide each time if you accept them or not. By disabling cookies, however, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

This site contains links to other websites, whether owned or controlled by Zurmo affiliates or unrelated third parties. Please note that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from those listed here. Zurmo is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any website you may visit.

**Privacy Policy Updates**

By using this site, you agree to the Zurmo.org online privacy policy. We may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, please check back periodically. User’s continued access to the Site and Services will indicate user has accepted the change.
